http://www.newspapersoc.org.uk/privacy

Privacy
We understand the importance or maintaining and protecting your privacy and will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for an event, subscribing to a newsletter, or downloading information we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling in an online form. The information you provide will be kept confidential and will be used to support your relationship with us. From time to time we may use this information to provide you with relevant information we think would be of particular interest. At a minimum we will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing. We will follow local requirements, such as allowing you to opt in before receiving unsolicited contact, where applicable.We use information we hold about you to monitor the use of the site and to keep records of traffic flows to the site. This may be by using a "cookie" or small piece of information stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. The cookies that we use contain no personal information that could be used to identify you. It is possible to configure your browser so that cookies are not used automatically but this may prevent you from having the benefit of some of the site's features.We work closely with other organisations and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, sending postal mail and email, and customer service. They are provided with personal information necessary to perform the task and may not use it for any other purpose.Account and other personal information will be released by us when we believe it is necessary to comply with law.This site includes links to other sites which we consider may be of interest to you. We cannot and have not reviewed all of the sites linked to this site and cannot be liable for their content. Users link to other sites at their own risk and use such sites according to the terms and conditions of use of such sites.By using the website you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this policy.
News Media Association - As part of its mission to champion the news media industry, the NMA promotes the activities of local and national media marketing bodies Local Media Works and Newsworks.
News Media AssociationSecond Floor16 - 18 New Bridge StreetLondonEC4V 6AG
T: +44 (0) 203 848 9620E: nma@newsmediauk.org@newsmediaorg
DisclaimerPrivacy & CookiesCopyrightContact
Website by Senior
The NMA uses cookies on its website. These are necessary for the website to function. We don’t use any cookies for the purposes of marketing, or pass on any information to third parties. Cookie information is available on the Privacy and Cookies page, where you will also find our Privacy Policy.
Continue to website
